{
    "results":[
            {
            "question":"In the bible, how many Plagues of Egypt were there?",
            "correct_answer": 10
        },
        {
            "question":"Which number Apollo mission was the spaceflight that landed the first two men on the Moon?",
            "correct_answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question":"Which number Pennsylvania Avenue is the formal address of the White House?",
            "correct_answer": 1600
        },
        {
            "question":"Charles Atlas marketed his fitness program for the 'how many' pound weakling?",
            "correct_answer": 97
        },
        {
            "question":"How much is in a Baker's Dozen?",
            "correct_answer": 13
        },
        {
            "question":"If an internet user follows a broken or dead link, they will typically find an error page with which number error message?",
            "correct_answer": 404
        },
        {
            "question":"How how many landlocked countries are there in South America?",
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question":"On most phones, what number key also features the letters M, N, and O?",
            "correct_answer": 6
        },
        {
            "question":"In inches, how high is a table tennis net?",
            "correct_answer": 6
        },
        {
            "question":"What do the sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel add up to?",
            "correct_answer": 666
        },
        {
            "question":"How many yards are there in a mile?",
            "correct_answer": 1760
        },
        {
            "question":"President Obama was what number President of the United States?",
            "correct_answer": 44
        },
        {
            "question":"What is an ogdoad?",
            "correct_answer": 8
        },
        {
            "question":"The EU Flag consists of a circle of how many golden stars?",
            "correct_answer": 12
        }
    ]
}